// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The nth term of an A.P. is given by an = 3 + 4n. The common difference is",
    answer: "4", // Answer and The Option with the correct answer should be pixel perfect
    options: [
      "7",
      "3", // Answer and the correct option
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "If p, q, r and s are in A.P. then r – q is",
    answer: "s - r",
    options: [
      "s - p",
      "s - q",
      "s - r",
      "None of these"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "If the sum of three numbers in an A.P. is 9 and their product is 24, then numbers are",
    answer: "2, 3, 4",
    options: [
      "2, 4, 6",
      "1, 5, 3",
      "2, 8, 4",
      "2, 3, 4"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The (n – 1)th term of an A.P. is given by 7,12,17, 22,… is",
    answer: "5n – 3",
    options: [
      "5n + 2",
      "5n + 3",
      "5n – 5",
      "5n – 3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The nth term of an A.P. 5, 2, -1, -4, -7 … is",
    answer: "8 – 3n",
    options: [
      "2n + 5",
      "2n - 5",
      "8 – 3n",
      "3n – 8"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The 10th term from the end of the A.P. -5, -10, -15,…, -1000 is",
    answer: "-955",
    options: [
      "-955",
      "-945",
      "-950",
      "-965"
    ]
  },
    {
  numb: 7,
  question: " Find the sum of 12 terms of an A.P. whose nth term is given by an = 3n + 4",
  answer: "262",
  options: [
    "262",
    "272",
    "282",
    "292"
    ]
  },
    {
  numb: 8,
  question: "The sum of all two digit odd numbers is",
  answer: "2475",
  options: [
    "2575",
    "2475",
    "2524",
    "2425"
    ]
  },
    {
  numb: 9,
  question: "The sum of first n odd natural numbers is",
  answer: "n²",
  options: [
    "2n²",
    "2n + 1",
    "2n – 1",
    "n²"
    ]
  },
    {
  numb: 10,
  question: "The number of multiples lie between n and n² which are divisible by n is",
  answer: "n - 2",
  options: [
    "n + 1",
    "n",
    "n - 1",
    "n - 2"
    ]
  }
];
